Finding Aid for the Avery Leiserson Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Publications
  - Urban Observatory of Metropolitan Nashville – University Centers, Program Report, May, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Fair Tax News, a publication of Tennesseans for Fair Taxation, March 1999; Summer, 1999; December 1999; April 2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - First Unitarian Universalist Church of Nashville, order of service, May 27, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C. 2003 (Box 8, Folder 22)